Manuscript (periodical) Records
Manuscript (periodical) Records
- Miscellanea
  - Printed material, 1932-1936; undated; 14 items (Box 4)
Garrett-Fields, W. Jr. Feb 16, 1934
Garvey, Flo [1936?] [1936?]
Garza, Luis V. Apr 10, 1935
Gaspar, Samuel Jun 29, 1934
Gastman, F.J. [Dec 6, 1934]
Gaylor, Leon J. Mar 9, 1934
Geiger, Julian Jan 19, 1935
Geiger, Milton E.M. Jul 31, 1935 Aug 31, 1935
Geisinger, Minna Oct 9, 1934
Gelles Advertising Agency Inc. [Dec 3, 1934]
Genden, Guanetta Apr 25, 1936
George, Mattie Kessler Oct 20, 1935
George, Selwyn undated
Ghene, J.A. Feb 12, 1935 May 11, 1935
Giertsen, Hazel M. Nov 8, 1935
Gill, Burgo D. Dec 15, 1934
Gilliam, Julia Apr 7, 1935
Gilman, Charlene Sep 16, 1935
Gilmore, Alice Dec 10, 1934, Dec 19, 1934
Gilsdorf, Frederick J. Mar 25, 1936 May 7, 1936
Giniger, Weldon Jun 27, 1934 Aug 16, 1934
Gipson, J.H. Jul 29, 1935
Gitlin, Murray Jul 16, 1934 Jul 23, 1934 Dec 27 [no year]
Glascott, Ruth Aug 27, 1934 [ca. Nov 30, 1934]
Glaspell, Susan Nov 17, 1936
Glass, J. Paul Sep 27, 1934
Glassheim, Louis L. Apr 30, 1935 [May 6, 1935]
Glassman and Solotoff Co. May 9, 1934 May 14, 1934
Gleason Marion [1934?]
Glenn, Alfred F. Aug 6, 1934 Dec 3, 1934
Glenn, Dorothy Feb 19, 1934
Glover, Harry S. Nov 25, 1934 Dec 3, 1934 Oct 10, 1935
Glover, Ira R. Mar 12, 1935 Feb 13 [no year]
Godin, Alexander Nov 2, 1936
Goldberg, Albert April 1, 1935 Nov 28, 1935 Jan 21, 1936
Golden, Bernard B. Jun 27, 1934
Goldenheime, L. Apr 2, 1935 Apr 16, 1935
Goldman, Sylvia C. [May 27, 1935]
Goldsmith, Beatrice Nov 4 [1935?] Nov 29, 1935
Goldsmith, Ida Nov 7, 1934
Goll, Frances E. Dec 4, 1933 Jan 31 [no year]
Gompf, Dennis Albert Dec 19, 1935
Goo, Mrs. G.H. undated
Goodman, Henry Jan 8, 1934 [Feb, 1934] Apr 7, 1934 Apr 7, 1934 [to Murrell Edmunds] Apr 27, 1934
Goodman, Steve Nov 20, 1934
Gordi, Tooni [Feb 14, 1935]
Gordon, Helen A. Feb 21, 1935
Gordon, John [Oct 12, 1934] undated
Gorman, Thomas Jun 28, 1934
Gosle, Frederic undated
Gotham Book Mart Mar 20, 1936
Gracey, Doris [Mar, 1934] Mar 11, 1934 Mar 30, 1934 May 26, 1934 Aug 17, 1935
Granel, Frank Anken May 19, 1934
Grant, Will B. Dec 3, 1934
Graves, W.L. Jan 6, 1934
Green, Frederick Mar 13, 1935 Jun 1, 1936
Green, Juliet Feb 15, 1936
Green, Stella E. [Feb 12, 1934]
Greenburg, Abraham Mar 11, 1935
Greenburg, Is— Aug 29, 1934
Griswell, Lloyd [1936?] Jan 21, 1936
Gronich, Mary T. Oct 29, 1934
Grosjean, Frank Oct 3, 1935
Grubb, Gena Dec 18, 1933
Gunn, Marjory Ryan Mar 11, 1935 Mar 30, 1935
Gurganus, Ransom Apr 30, 1935
Gurkin, Jean May 11, 1936
Gurney, Joseph Apr 12, 1935
Hall, Bernice Sep 26, 1934
Halverson, Bert Jul 24, 1936
Hamilton, R.L. Nov 25, 1934
Hansen, Joe Sep 14, 1935
Hanson, Bip Jul 28, 1934 Aug 27, 1934 [Sep 6, 1934] Oct 27 [1934] Nov 6 [1935] Dec 21, 1935 May 28, 1936 undated Jun 15 [no year]
Hanson, Merlin Oct 29 [no year]
Harkey, J.W. Feb 16 [1934]
Harney, Anna Louise Jan 16, 1934 Jan 30, 1934 Feb 18, 1934
Harper, Lawrence A. Feb 9, 1934 Apr 2, 1934 May 28, 1934 Jun 25, 1934 Oct 26, 1934 Feb 18, 1935 Sep 17, 1935 Jul 21, 1936 undated
Harper, Virginia Apr 4, 1935
Harrison, Jay Aug 31, 1934 Sep 16, 1934
Hartman, Art Apr 6, 1934 Aug 30, 1934 Feb 18, 1935 Sep 21, 1935
Haskell, Esther Nov 21, 1936
Hatcher, Harlan Sep 28, 1936 Oct 13, 1936 Nov 9, 1936 undated
Hathaway, Virginia Jan 27, 1936 May 30, 1936 Aug 2, 1936 Jan 20 [no year] Nov 30 [no year]
Hauser, Simon J. undated
Hauserman, Harold V. Oct 1, 1934 Nov 30, 1934
Hawksely, C.Y. Jun 14, 1935
Hawthorn, Eleanor May 26, 1934
Hays, Bernice Jan 14, 1936
Hazeltine, Eleanor L. Dec 30, 1933 Sep 25, 1934 Jan 22, 1935
Heal, Edith [Mrs. Gil Meynier] undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated
Heckelman, Charles N. Jul 26, 1934
Hegeman, Janet Feb 19, 1934
Hennig, Else Oct 14, 1936
Henning, Harry S. Dec 31, 1933
Henricksen, Grace M. Jan 7, 1934
Hepburn, Ethel Jun 19, 1936 Aug 1, 1936
Herbers, Katherine Mar 7 [1934]
Hermann, Eugene Sep 12, 1935 undated
Herron, Darrell Jan 9, 1934 Feb 3, 1936
Herron; Edwin undated
Hershey, Lloyd E. Feb 28, 1934
Hickok, Helen Mar 26, 1935 Mar 29, 1935 May 11, 1935 Jul 15, 1935 Jul 22, 1935 Sep 8, 1935 Nov 11, 1935 Mar 12, 1936
Hicks, Clifton [1936?]
Hill, Martha Sorina Apr 26, 1934
Hill, William H. Apr 2, 1936
Nilton, Charles Jun 24, 1934
Hinckley, Samuel N. Nov 19, 1936
Hines, Edna Jun 2, 1934
Hinkhouse, Mabel Mar 22, 1934
Hisbane, John D. Jan 15, 1934
Hite, W.M. [ca. 1934]
Hoff, George L. Aug 11, 1936
Hogan, Donovan L. Sep 29, 1934 Oct 9, 1934
Hogan, William undated
Holmes, Doris Apr 4, 1934
Hooper, Grace Duncan Jun 6, 1934
Horkan, Mrs. P.D. Feb 15, 1934
Horner, John W. Jun 7, 1934
Horsley, Caperton Apr 18, 1934 May 3, 1934 May 18, 1934 Oct 14, 1934 Dec 5, 1934 Feb 27, 1935 Apr 29, 1935 undated
House, Madeline E. Jul 19, 1934
Howard, Arthur W. Jan 17, 1935
Hubbard, Elizabeth Dec 7, 1933
Huber, Charles E. May 28, 1934
Huddleston, Warren C. [Aug 6, 1935] undated
Hudeburg, Charles E. Feb 2, 1934 Mar 3, 1934 [Nov 10, 1934] undated undated
Huggins, Luella A. Jul 18, 1936 Aug 8, 1936
Hughes, Edward R. Jun 2, 1934
Husband, John Dillon May 3, 1935
Hutchens, Jane Mar 2, 1935 undated
Hyatt, Robert M. Jul 16, 1934
Hyde, Art Sep 15, 1934 Sep 21, 1935
Ice, Orva Lee Dec 10, 1935
Ike, Carl B. [Nov 8, 1934]
Ingall, V.H. May 28, 1934
Irwin, Theodore Oct 31, 1936 [ca. Nov 1936]
Isbell, Bernetta Mar 22, 1934
Ivedale, Lucille Jan 30, 1935
Jackson, Helen E. undated
Jacob, Clary F. Nov 11, 1934 Jan 14, 1936
Jacobs, Elijah Aug 26, 1934 Feb 3, 1935
Jacobs, Martha Dec 18, 1933
Jacobs, Robert W. [Aug 6? 1934]
Jacobson, Elizabeth Dec 28, 1933 [1934?] [ca. 1934] undated undated
Jacobson, Nicholas Biel Dec 9, 1934 undated undated undated undated
Jacque, Elizabeth Sep 14, 1934 Oct 19, 1934 Jan 28, 1935 Jul 2 [no year]
James, Eva McKinnie [ca. May, 1934]
Jandron, Ellis May 12, 1936
Jansen, Louise Oct 21, 1934 Oct 18, 1935
Janson, Don Oct 15, 1935
Jay, Alice Jun 19, 1936
Jenkins, Herbert F. Mar 23, 1936 May 14, 1936 Jul 10, 1936 Aug 17, 1936
Jessop, Kenneth Apr 17, 1934
Jessup, Mildred K. undated [Joason?], Don Easter [1935?]
Johns, Richard Feb 19, 1934 Mar 15, 1934 Jan 7, 1935 Jul 9, 1935
Johnson, Bolt Apr 17, 1934 May 11, 1934 Jun 24, 1934
Johnson, Eiton Jan 18, 1936
Johnson, Horace W. Jun 22, 1934 Dec 24, 1934
Johnson, Jean Aug 16, 1935
Johnson, Lucy D. Mar 2, 1934
Johnson, Marvel Dunn May 9, 1935
Johnson, Maurice 0. Jul 30, 1935
Johnson, Robert Sep 27, 1934 Oct 21, 1934 Nov 11, 1934 Mar 26, 1935
Johnston, M.C. Dec 4, 1934
Jones, — Dec 21, 1936
Jones, Carless Jan 16, 1935 Apr 10, 1935
Jones, Everett Jan 28, 1934 [To Jack Ramsey?] May 29, 1934 Jun 29, 1934 Jul 10, 1934 Jul 16, 1934 Aug 4, 1934 Aug 27, 1934 Sep 12, 1934 Oct 6, 1934 Oct 16, 1934 Nov 11, 1934 Nov 12, 1934 Nov 26, 1934 [Dec, 1934] [1935?] Jan 28, 1935 [ca. Mar 1935] Mar 12, 1935 Apr 13, 1935 Apr 20, 1935 Apr 26, 1935 May 1, 1935 May 10, 1935 Jun 10, 1935 Jun 11, 1935 Jun 14, 1935 Jul 10, 1935 Jul 12, 1935 Jul 18, 1935 Aug 24, 1935 Sep 5, 1935 Jan, 1936
Jones, J. undated
Jones, Mary Louise Jan 6, 1934
Jones, Myron S. Oct 5, 1935
Jones, Willis K. Dec 22, 1933 Mar 1, 1934
Jordt, Agnes C. May 20, 1935 Oct 23, 1935
Joseph, Don Apr 17, 1934
Kahn, Lawrence R. Feb 21, 1934
Kale, D.V. Oct 24, 1934
Kampf, E.P. undated
Kantor, Helen Rich Feb 9, 1934 Mar 7, 1934 Apr 2, 1934 May 14, 1934 Dec 27, 1934 Dec 19, 1935 Jan 18, 1936 Aug 26 [no year]
Kapingen, Rose Mar 4, 1935 Mar 13, 1935 Mar 21, 1935 Apr 8, 1935 Apr 24, 1935 May 13, 1935 Jun 5, 1935 Jun 10, 1935 Jun 20, 1935 Jul 2, 1935 Jul 8, 1935 Aug 1, 1935 Sep 18, 1935 Nov 19, 1935 Mar 10 [no year] Dec 7 [no year]
Kaplan, Philip Jan 24, 1934 Feb 7, 1934 Mar 6, 1934 Jun 6, 1934 Jul 19, 1934
Karpeles, Madelaine Jan 1, 1934
Kash, Christine Aug 9, 1934
Kates, Patricia F. Jan 8 [ca. 1934]
Kauser, Alice Oct 23, 1935 Sep 2, 1936 Sep 28, 1936
Kay, Neil May 3, 1934
Kees, Weldon Aug 2 [1934?] Aug 16, 1934 Oct 10 [1934] Jan 18, 1935 Feb 18, 1935 Mar 16, 1935 Mar 27, 1935 May 17, 1935 May 24, 1935 Aug 11, 1935 Nov 15, 1935 Dec 16, 1935 Feb 18, 1936 Apr 10, 1936 Jul 5, 1936 Aug 4, 1936 Aug 12, 1936 Sep 18, 1936 Dec 9, 1936 undated undated undated undated
Kieth, Joseph Joel Jul 26, 1934 Jan 9, 1935 Apr 1, 1935 Apr 2, 1935
Kiethley, M. Maddox undated
Kelly, Merritt Apr 12, 1935
Kelm, Karlton [Oct, 1934?] [Dec 16, 1934] [Dec 22, 1934] [Dec 27, 1934] [Jan 26, 1935] [Mar 15, 1935] [Sep 19, 1935] undated undated undated Feb 23 [no year] [Mar 8, no year.]
Kelm, William E. [ca. Mar 24, 1934]
Kielt, Norman undated [To Abbot S. Cohen] undated undated
Kieth and Kiethley (see page 34)
Kilbourne, Irene Feb 6, 1935 "Kirch" [Jan, 1934] undated
Kirk, Franklyn Jul 25, 1935 Sep 3, 1935 Feb 9, 1936 Jun 4, 1936 Jul 22 [1936?] Aug 27, 1936 Sep 11 [1936?] Sep 17, 1936 Oct 15, 1936 [Nov 11], 1936 [Nov 26], 1936 Dec 3, 1936
Kirk, W.R. Feb 20, 1934
Kirkbride, Ronald undated undated Dec 12 [no year]
Kirkpatrick, Doris Jul 18, 1936
Kischer, Rolf Dec 2, 1933
Kissinger, Margaret Sep 17, 1934
Knight, R. Javereth Mar 15, 1934
Kohl, J.G. Jul 14, 1934
Kohle, Rita Sears undated
Kolar, Josephine Jul 23, 1934
Kozlenko, William Feb 17, 1934 Apr 11, 1934 Jun 5, 1934 Nov 14, 1934
Kraike, Michel Dec 16, 1933 Dec 29, 1933 Jan 24, 1934 Feb 7, 1934 [Mar, 1934] May 2, 1934 Jun 28, 1934 Aug 19, 1934 Nov 12, 1934. Dec 19, 1934 May l5 [no year]
Krantz, David E. Mar 18, 1935 May 20, 1936
Kreps[?], Kenneth Feb 2, 1934
Krotz, Elsie Jul 11, 1934
La Costa, Richard Mar 25, 1936
Lakser, Leo Mar 10, 1935
Lamb, Joseph [Sep 30, 1934]
Lambert, Grace E. Apr 9, 1934
Lampe, Alan Mar 4, 1935
Lancaster, Paul C. Dec 17, 1933
Landau, Noah Sep 5, 1936 Nov 28, 1936
Laney, John Charles Apr 9, 1934
Langford, Gerald Feb 11, 1935 Mar 12, 1935 Apr 8, 1935 Apr 24, 1936
Larson, A.G. Mar 3, 1934
Larson, Earling Jun 4, 1934 Oct 10, 1934 Jan 4, 1936 Jan 20, 1936
Laughlin, C.J. Feb 5, 1934
Laughlin, James Nov 28 [no year]
Lawrence, Elsie B. Oct 19, 1935 May 14, 1936 May 29, 1936 Aug 4, 1936 Sep 8, 1936 Sep 21, 1936 undated
Leder, J. Michael [1934] Sep 23, 1935
Leidinger, M. Rosalie Dec 22, 1933
Levy, F.S. May 8, 1934
Levy, Helen May 1, 1936 May 14, 1936 May 20, 1936
Lewis, Bert M. Feb 17, 1934
Lewis, Dorothy [ca. 1933, 1934]
Lewis, John W. Aug 17, 1934
Lick, Maxine U. Apr 28, 1934
Ligocki, Michael Jun 29, 1936 Sep 18, 1936
Lindberg, Marcella Apr 6, 1935 Aug 9, 1935
Linderman, Annik [ca. 1934]
Lipkin, Florence Mar 1, 1934 Jun 4, 1934 Sep 22, 1934 Oct 19, 1934 Jun 10, 1935 Oct 27, 1935 Jan 12, 1936
Locke, William Apr 27, 1934
Lodge, Nora Apr 3, 1934
Lord, David Mar 9, 1935
Lorenz, Martha Dec 18, 1933
Lucas, Allen Jun 11, 1936
Lumen, Beckett Mar 1, 1936
Lutch, Arthur Oct 2, 1934
Lyon, Marjorie May 9, 1936
Mabie, L.F. undated
MacCallum, Russell Dec 10, 1933 [1934?] Jan 24, 1934
McCalmon, Chas. A. Mar 15, 1934
MacCampbell, Donald Feb 13, 1936 [Nov, 1936] undated
McCarthy., Thomas J. Jan 22, 1934
MacCaul, W.T. Mar 21, 1934
McCullough, Marvin Jun 27, 1935 Mar 16, 1936
McCurley, I. [Oct 28, 1934]
McCutcheon, Margaret Mar 7, 1934
McDermott, John Dec 18, 1933
MacDonald, Eudora G. Jun 12, 1934 Jul 16, 1936
McElnee, William April [ca. 1934]
McElroy, Kimball Jan 30, 1935 Mar 29, 1935
McFarland, Hector J. Jul 15, 1935
McGinnis, Allen Aug 27, 1934 Oct 6, 1934 Apr 11, 1935 Jun 7, 1935
MacGregor, Martha Aug 10 [no year]
McKee, Ruth E. Mar 20, 1934 Jun 11, 1934 Jul 10, 1934
McKenzie, Vernon Feb 23, 1935
Mackey, Rev. William K. Mar 26, 1935
McKusick, Rosa Oct 20, 1934
MacMillan,[M ] Mar 5, 1934
McNaught, Mrs. S.P. Jan 6, 1934
McQuarrie, Lillian Nov 2, 1934 Apr 21, 1936 May 28, 1936 Aug 1, 1936
Maddox, M. Fern Feb 27, 1934
Maitland, Ralph Feb 17, 1935 undated undated undated undated undated undated
Makepeace, John May 15, 1936
Mallen, Lloyd Feb 16, 1935
Mamet, Louis [1934?] Feb 1, 1934 [Mar, 1934] Mar 13, 1934 Jun 13, 1936 Sep 17, 1936 Oct 27, 1936 undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated
Manch, Joseph Rodman May 16, 1934 May 23, 1934 Aug 6, 1934 May 11, 1935 Jan 7, 1936 Feb.6, 1936
Mangan, Sherry Sep 22, 1934 Feb 3, 1935
Manheimer, I.S. Oct 21, 1935
Marfione, Jerre undated
Mark, Norma [1934?] Feb 9, 1934 [Mar 12, 1934] Dec, 1934 undated undated undated [fragment]
Martin, Bernice Arden Mar 18, 1935 Mar 27, 1935 Apr 17, 1935
Martin, Curtis Jan 31, 1935 May 13, 1935 Oct 7, 1935 Nov 13, 1935 Jan 6, 1936 Feb 11, 1936 Jun 4, 1936
Martin, James B. Mar 30, 1934
Masselman, George Mar 3, 1937
Mathieu, Aron M. Dec 11, 1935 Jan 15, 1936 Jan 25, 1936 Jan 30, 1936 Feb 15, 1936 undated
Matsoukas, Nick John undated
Mattison, Lewis Mar 10, 1934
Maud, William Jun 3, 1935
Maxson, Virginia Jun 28, 1934
Mayer, Albert Jr. Aug 27, 1934
Mayer, Stanley Dehler Feb 3, 1934 Feb 24, 1934 Aug 23, 1934
Mayham, F.B. Feb 17, 1934
Mead, David Jun 18, 1935
Meade, Everard Feb 4, 1934 Mar 9, 1936
Mechfessel, William Jun 25, 1934
Meeter, George F. Jan 16, 1934 Jan 24, 1934 Feb 4, 1934 Mar 13, 1934 Apr 2, 1934 May 4, 1934 May 25, 1934 Jun 8, 1934 Ju117, 1934 Sep 1, 1934 Sep 11, 1934 Oct 5, 1934 Oct 26, 1934 undated
Meissl, Mary Jul 20,1934
Mendes, Alfred [Jun 2, 1934] Jun 26, 1934 Jul 2, 1934 Feb 25, 1935 Mar 19, 1935
Menkel, Tom Nov 5, 1934 Jan, 1935
Mercer, Mary Aug 9, 1935 Nov 19, 1935 Jan 25, 1936 Mar 16, 1936 May 5, 1936 Dec 20 [no year]
Merrill, Irene Mar 8 [1934?] Apr 2 [1934?] Nov 1 [1934] Aug 10, 1935 Feb 9 [no year]
Mets, William J. Mar 17, 1934
Meynier, Edith Heal See Heal, Edith
Meynier, Gil Aug 29, 1934 undated
Meyrowitz, B.C. undated
Middendorf, Barbara Oct 5, 1934
Miller, Emmett C. Mar 21 [1935]
Miller, Fred R. Jul 7, 1935 Jun 20, 1936 Sep 7, 1936 Jan 15, 1936 Jul 21, 1936 Aug 13 [no year] Nov 21 [no year] Jan 7 [no year] Jan 25, 1935 May 20, 1934
Miller, Henry undated 1935
Millinger, Louise Feb 26, 1935 Jan 16, 1936 Apr 20, 1936
Millington, John Apr 30, 1934
Miskell, A.J. Feb 20, 1935 Oct 15, 1935
Mitchell, Stanley Jun 6, 1934
Moe, Henry Allen Oct 30, 1934 Nov 7, 1934
Mohan, I.M. [Aug 13, 1934]
Moll, Ed A. Jun 2, 1936 Oct 30, 1936 undated
Mooney, Booth Feb 5, 1934
Moore, H.G. [Mar 5, 1934]
Moore, Hilda Nov 24, 1936
Morang, Alfred Dec 2, 1933 Dec 9, 1933 Jan 16, 1934 May 25, 1934 Jul 13, 1934 Jun 4, 1935 Nov 8, 1935 May 28, 1936 Jul 1, 1936
Morenus, Constance Gay [May, 1934] May 29, 1934 Nov 7, 1934
Morgan, Mildred Sep 16, 1934
Morris, S.S. [May 17, 1934]
Morrison, Theodore Mar 21, 1934 Mar 25, 1936
Morse, Irl Nov 10, 1936
Morton, Maxwell Sep 22, 1934
Moseley, Elizabeth C. Feb 12, 1934
Moser, Edna Robert Oct 4, 1935 Sep 26, 1936
Mossman, Mereb E. Oct 8, 1935
Munson, Fleet [Nov 26, 1934] [Dec 1, 1934] Dec 14, 1934 Jan 22, 1935 undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated [fragment] undated [fragment] undated [fragment] undated [fragment] Feb 13, 1935 [fragment] [To Elmer Dingeldey] undated [fragment] [To Elmer Dingeldey]
Muntz, Herbert Jan 31, 1934
Murphy, Helen A. Apr 26, 1934
Musfeldt, Gordon W. Jul 25, 1936
Myers, Marjorie Oct 10, 1934
Myers, Nancy M. Spaford Apr 18, 1934
Neff, Howard C. Aug 28, 1934
Nieman, Egbert Jul 30, 1934
Norwood, Hayden E. Aug 8, 1934
O'Brian, Mary Ann Dec 19, 1933
O'Byrne, Emmet undated
O'Donnell, George Marion Sep 5, 1934
O'Farrel, C. J. Oct 13, 1934
O'Neill, Frances Morton Sep 16, 1934
Otto, J. undated
Owen, Paul Jul 5, 1934
Owens, Florence Jul 27, 1934
Packard, Harriet Sep 4, 1934
Palmer, Frank E. Apr 23, 1934
Panknin, Frederick A. Sep 15, 1934
Payette, Madeleine [Oct 25, 1934]
Perman, M. Jun 13, 1934
Phelps, Ruth H. Apr 26, 1934
Phillips, Josephine E. Jan 25, 1934
Phillips, Wendell (fl.1934) Jun 2, 1934
Pickett, Lyndell S. Feb 12, 1934
Pico, Jennie Feb 15, 1934
Pigg, E.L. Mar 22, 1934
Plumleigh, Grove Mar 31, 1934
Potts, Mary Donnell Jan 5, 1934
Powell, Clarence Alva Sep 28, 1934
Preil, Sarah R. Dec 18, 1933
Purssell, Eleanor M. Apr 7, 1934
Quarrie, Lillian M. Dec 10, 1934
Ramsey, John May 23, 1934
Ranelle, Stella Apr 19, 1934
Rapport, Howard W. Jun 3, 1934
Ray, Agnes [ca. 1934]
Reed, R.M. Feb 3, 1936
Reeder, Pauline S. [ca. 1934]
Reider, Curtis H. [ca. 1934]
Reiser, M.J. Jun 1, 1934
Renstein, Herman Aug 22, 1936
Renwick, Cyra May 21, 1934
Rey, Rita Apr 11, 1934
Rhodes, Mary K. Oct 4, 1934
Riaska, Jack Jul 28, 1934
Richer, Hervey [Feb 8, 1934]
Rieler, Hope [ca. 1934]
Riley, Edith M. [Feb 14, 1934]
Rimington, Critchell Nov 21, 1935
Rivers, Jean Mar 17, 1934 Apr 16, 1934 [May 24, 1934] undated Jun 22 [no year] Jul 24 [no year]
Robeson, Audrey Feb 19, 1934
Robinson, Dorothy Clapp [ca. 1934]
Robinson, Mrs. J.L. Sep 16, 1934.
Robinson, Lillian C. Jan 20, 1934
Rogers, Jean [ca. 1934]
Rogerson, Thomas Jun 6, 1934
Roochnik, A. Aug 28, 1934
Rood, John Oct 22, 1934 [To D.A. Davidson] Nov 1, 1934 [To Mary Gronich] Jan 11, 1936 [To William Carlos Williams]
Rose, A.A. Oct 1 [1934?]
Rose, Jules N. Jan 2, 1934
Rosemond, R.R. Oct 14, 1934
Rosenberg, Irvin Jun 8, 1934
Rosenfeld, Emanuel Sep 21, 1934
Russell, Mary Margaret Dec 30, 1933
St. John, C.S. Feb 26, 1936
Salak, Joseph C. Feb 2, 1934
Salt, Sydney May 21, 1934 [May 24, 1934] Jun 23, 1934 undated
Samms, Marie Feb, 1934
Sampson, Charles [ca. 1934]
Samuel, Mrs. John E. Dec 18, 1933
Sandburg, Lee [ca. Aug 22, 1934]
Scanland, J.M. Aug 1, 1934
Schaaf, K.A. Aug 28, 1934
Schultz, Edward M. Feb 11, 1935
Schwander, P.W. [May 15, 1934]
Schwartz, Felix C. Apr 14, 1934
Scribner, Frederick Jul 9, 1934
Seely, Jane Stoddard [ca. 1934]
Shaffer, Kenneth R. Apr 4, 1934
Sherman, Irving undated
Siddall, Alice Jun 11 [1934]
Sieglar, Howard W. May 13, 1934
Simpson, Hariette May 21, 1933
Sims, Hattie Stone Feb 6, 1934
Sinclair, Miriam E. Jul 20, 1934
Singerman, Deborah [ca. 1934]
Sisk, Frank Sep 1, 1934
Slough, Betty Jane Jan 22, 1934
Smith, C.W. Mar 6, 1934
Smith, Eldon Emerson Apr 18, 1934
Smith, Ellen Griffith Mar 26, 1934 Apr 14, 1934
Smith, Ethel [ca. 1934]
Smith, Gordon Bruce Sep 27, 1934
Smith, Margaret Mar 15, 1934
Snell, George Dixon III Jan 18, 1934
Snow, Jack Jun 17, 1934
Snyder, Leonard undated
Snyder, Russel [ca. 1934]
Souba, Jane Oct 13, 1934
Sparks, William Sheppard Aug 15, 1934
Sparrow, Louise Kidder Mar 9, 1934
Speck, Nathaniel Sep 29, 1934
Standard, Irving Jul 21, 1934
Steer, A.B. Dec 6, 1934
Steinbrenner, Ed W. [ca. 1934]
Steinke, John Aug 28, 1934
Sterling, Alexander Mahan Jun 19, 1934
Stern, Seymour Jan 30, 1934
Stevens, Alden Clifford [ca. 1934]
Stewart, Winifred Gray [Oct 11, 1934]
Stockman, Goldie Feb 28, 1934
Stone, — Feb 20, 1934
Stone, Donald H. [Jan 29, 1934] Feb 14, 1934
Stossel, Harold E. Mar 25, 1934
Stott, Cecil Gordon Jul 16, 1934
Stresnic, S.N. [Jun 9, 1934]
Stuart, Virginia May 29, 1934
Sutton, Kathleen [ca. 1934]
Swindell, Roberta [ca. 1934]
Sydney, P.B. Jun 25, 1934
Taylor, Bruce O. Jan 30, 1934
Teeter, Mary E. Jan 19, 1935 Feb 22, 1935
Thomas, Charles [ca. 1934]
Thompson, Dan [ca. 1934]
Tichenor, Edwin B. Jul 6, 1934
Tinker, George H. Mar 26, 1934
Tobin, Charles S. May 24, 1934
Todd, Marie Aug 22, 1934
Toney, O'Connell [Jan 11, 1934]
Traboulsee, Anthony Feb 22, 1934
Tracy, Elise Mar 1, 1934
Tregenza, Lillian Mar 16, 1934
Trommer, Marie Jan 15, 1934
Tubaugh, R.D. Dec 30, 1933
Tucker, James David Feb 1, 1934
Turbitt, A.E. Oct 22, 1934
Turner, P.T. [ca. 1934]
Tzirlin, Belle undated
Vail, Helen C. undated
Valyear, Howard Jul 24, 1934
Van Horne, Ruth G. Dec 26, 1934
Van Zindran, Anneke Feb 18, 1935 Mar 12, 1935 Sep 16, 1935
Vaughan, Thos. Dec 19, 1933
Venturini, Elsie Jul 2, 1934
Ver Duft, Leo Apr 16, 1934 Jun 13, 1935 Sep 18, 1935 Nov 19, 1935
Vickrey, Emma Mae May 12, 1934
Vinci, Albert Edward Feb 5, 1934
Von Hellmer, Hilda [Wullen] Dec 20, 1933 Jun 15, 1935
Wagner, Helen Ruth Jul 25, 1934
Waldron, Winifred Mar 7, 1934
Walfert, Helen Dec 16, 1934
Walker, Frank deBrisay Apr 8, 1935
Walker, Marion K. Jul 23, 1936
Wallace, Irving May 4, 1935 Dec 20, 1935
Waller, George Jr. Oct 4, 1934
Wallester, David Nov 3, 1935
Walley, H.R. Mar 9, 1934
Walls, Callie K. Dec 4, 1933 Dec 27, 1933 Jan 11, 1934 undated
Walsh, Catherine Jul 15 [no year]
Walsh, Emily M. Dec 2, 1934
Walters, Eve Nov 9, 1934 Nov 14, 1934 Dec 4, 1934 Jan 22, 1935 May 27, 1935 Oct 3, 1935
Ward, William Allen Apr 3, 1936 Apr 3, 1936
Warner, Ella G. Jan 15, 1935 Jan 18, 1936
Warner, Robert Jul 25, 1935
Warwick, Rhoda Richards Jun 12, 1934
Waters, Vera Feb 24, 1934
Watkins, Edmund Dec 26, 1934
Watts, W.H.J. Jul 8, 1936 Aug 24, 1936 [Oct 6, 1936] Oct 25, 1936 Apr 23 [no year]
Waugh. Mildred Ockert Jun 12, 1935
Weaver, J. Howard Apr 17, 1935
Weaver, Ralph E. Dec 19, 1935
Webb, Jon Edgar Mar 9, 1936 [Apr 25, 1936]
Webster, Mary Shannon Mar 26, 1934
Webster, Ramona Mar 17, 1936
Weidman, Jerome Mar 25, 1934
Weigel, Henriette Mar 16, 1936 Apr 14, 1936
Weldon, Helen Oct 30, 1935 undated
Wellington, Grace Kemmerling Mar 22, 1934 Apr, 1934 Jun 16, 1934 Oct 12, 1934 Dec 20, 1934 [Jan 10, 1935] Feb 7, 1935
Wesley, Cecile Cobb undated 1935
Westbrook, Ira E. undated
Westhoff, Helen H. Jan 14, Feb 5, 1935 Feb 23, 1935
Wharton, Elizabeth Houghton Jan 5, 1935 Jan 21, 1935 Jan 28, 1935
Wharton, James B. Dec 18, 1934
Wheeler, Paul W. Apr 18, 1934
Whitcomb, Ellen Sep 26, 1934
Whitcomb, Robert Mar 29, 1934
White, — Sep 21, 1934
White, Robb III Aug 15, 1935 Sep 24, 1935 Feb 27, 1934 Dec 18, 1934 Jan 22, 1935
White, Sarah Harrison Jun 3, 1936
Whitehand, Robert Apr 4, 1935 Apr 16, 1935 undated
Whitely, Mary N.S. Sep 9, 1935
Whiting, Betty Jul 23, 1934
Whitney, Elizabeth May 19, 1936 Jun 19, 1936 Aug 1, 1936 Aug 17, 1936
Wikander, Gunnar Jan 8, 1934
Wilcox, Nathan H. undated
Wilcox, Wendell [ca. 1934]
Wilde, Irene [ca. 1934]
Wilder, Charlotte May 6, 1935
Wilfer, George May 23, 1935
Willette, Alfred Sep 12, 1934
Willette, Florence Hynes Feb 22, 1934 Mar 27, 1934
Williams, B.Y. Jan 25, 1934 Mar 10, 1934 Mar 13, 1934
Williams, Blanch Colton Apr 24, 1934
Williams, Janet Moore Jul 24, 1935 Feb 19, 1936 Apr 11, 1936 Mar 29 [no year]
Williams, Richard Martin Dec 30 [no year]
Williams, William Carlos Jan 11, 1936
Willis, Ruth Oct 4, 1934
Willms, Emilie Jun 3, 1935
Wills, Harry Snyder Aug 25, 1935
Willson, M.A. Dec 9, 1935
Wilson, G.E. Jul 2, 1934
Wilson, Howard Aaron Mar 6, 1936
Wilson, Rachel Mack [ca. 1934] Oct 19, 1934 undated
Winslow, Kathryn Apr 14, 1934 Oct 1, 1934 Nov 30, 1934 Jan 29, 1936
Winslow, Walter Sep 27, 1934 May 4, 1935 Sep 30 [no year]
Winter, Dorthea E. May 2, 1934
Wiser, Milton U. Sep 23, 1936
Wolf, E. Christian Jun 5, 1934
Wolf, Hilda Mar 4, 1935
Wood, Louise Jul 31, 1934
Wood, W.M. Feb 4, 1935
Woods, Ruth Cecelia Dec 12, 1933 undated
Woods, William Thomas Jan 16, 1936
Woodside, Mrs. Hal May 14, 1936
Woskow, Hilda Feb 6, 1935 May 29, 1935
Wrench, Alfred Dec 30, 1934
Wrenn, Eric undated
Wright, H.G. Jun 4, 1934
Writzel, Audrey M. Dec 15, 1934
Yeager, Christine Oct 26, 1934 Sep 25, 1935 Oct 22, 1935
Yeisley, W.H. [Jan 8, 1935]
Yezbak, Jake J. [ca. 1934] Jan 12, 1934 Jan 14, 1934 Jan 18, 1934 Feb 20, 1935 [Oct 23, 1935] [Apr 16, 1936] [May 5, 1936] May 14, 1936 undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated
Yordon, Philip undated
Young, L.K. Dec 15, 1935
Young, Lucy D. May 18, 1934
[Young], Pearl Dec 26, 1933 Apr 23, 1934 Apr 2 [no year] Jun 16 [no year]
Youngquist, W.E. Mar 7, 1935
Yourfair, Joyce undated 1936
Yuhasz, Johnny Jun 19,
Zeller, Winn F. Mar 25, 1934
Zetzer, Ruth Aug 16, 1935.
Zeydal, Richard Oct 7, 1935
Zick, Edgar Jun 25, 1935 Jul 10, 1935
Zielinski, Mabel undated 1934
Zillerman, Ruth I. Sep 26,
Zimmer, J. Oct 3, 1934
Zirinsky, Evelyn Nov 7, 1934
Zottarelli, Helena Fay Oct 31, 1934 Nov 24, 1934
Zupan, Stanley Aug 28, 1935